thefreebiesource.com 2012-10-14

# The Freebie Source » Privacy Policy

To sum it up for you quickly, thefreebiesource.com does not sell users information. We are committed to protecting your privacy

We will not sell, disseminate, disclose, transmit, transfer, share, lease, or rent any personally identifiable information to any third party not specifically authorized by you to receive your information except as we have disclosed to you in this Privacy Policy and in our Legal Notice.

 **The Information We Collect About You and How We Use It**

When you enter our website, we automatically collect and store certain information such as:

• Your IP address and domain name.

• The type of browser and operating system you use.

• The time and length of your visit.

• The pages of our site you visit.

• Data on searches you perform.

This information is used for administrative and technical purposes. Such purposes could include counting the number of visitors to our site and individual pages within the site, determining referral sources to our website, assessing the technology used to access our site, and assisting with site maintenance.

 **Information Collection**

When you send us an email, subscribe to email updates for The Freebie Source, or register on The Freebie Source, you will provide us with certain personally identifiable information including your email address. To make comments, you will be asked to supply name or nickname, email address, and website (not required).

 **Cookies**

A cookie is a piece of data that is stored on a visitor’s hard drive while visiting The Freebie Source. We use **cookies** to identify one unique visitor from another visitor, to store a visitor’s preferences, and to record session information in order to provide customized webpage content and better service when a visitor returns.

 **Third-Party Links and Advertising**

The Freebie Source may contain third-party advertising and links to third-party websites that are not controlled by The Freebie Source. The third-party advertising and links are made available to our readers as a convenience. Please be aware that The Freebie Source is not responsible for the content of third-party advertising and websites, nor are we responsible for the privacy policy or practices of third- **parties** and their websites. Our Privacy Policy only applies to information we collect from you while you are actively in session with The Freebie Source. If you should link to a third-party website from The Freebie Source, we strongly encourage you to review and become familiar with that website’s privacy policy.

 **Third-Party Services**

From time to time, we may engage third- **parties** to assist in providing marketing, back-end, programming and support services. These third- **parties** will only have access to information to the extent necessary to provide such services.

 **No Disclosure of Personal Information**

Except as specified above, we do not intend to disclose any personal information about you to any third-party without prior consent unless we have a good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (i) complete your transaction; (ii) comply with legal process or other legal requirements of any governmental authority; (iii) protect and defend our rights or property; and (iv) enforce the terms and conditions on The Freebie Source. We may provide certain information in aggregate form collected from you, and relating to you, to third- **parties**. However, we will not provide any personally identifying information.

 **Postings**

We have no control over who reads your postings, or what other users may do with the information you voluntarily post, so please use caution when posting any personal information or comments.

 **Business Transfer**

Although we have no plans to transfer The Freebie Source, if that were to happen, we may share your information in a business transfer. As with any other business, we could merge with, or be acquired by another company. If this occurs, the successor company would perhaps acquire the information we maintain, including personally identifiable information.

 **Changes in Our Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy without providing advance notice of our intent to make the changes. We may change this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the revised Privacy Policy in the “Privacy Policy” section of the website. The revised Privacy Policy is effective immediately when posted on The Freebie Source. It is the responsibility of each user to review the website and the Privacy Policy periodically to learn of any revisions to this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the website after the effectiveness of such revisions will constitute your acknowledgment and acceptance of the terms of the revised Privacy Policy.

 **Questions**  
If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us by using by using the form located below
